# THERESA BENNETT

Theresabennett@hotmail.ca | 416-820-2675 | North York ON M2M 0B1

### **SUMMARY**

Personable and dedicated Customer Service Representative with extensive experience in retail and administrative roles. Solid team player with upbeat, positive attitude and motivated to maintain customer satisfaction and contribute to company success. Articulate, enthusiastic and results-oriented with demonstrated passion for building relationships, cultivating partnerships and growing businesses.

### SKILLS

- Time Management
- Work Prioritization
- Utilizes all available resources to achieve optimal results
- Inbound and Outbound Calling Teamwork and Collaboration Strong
- Strong Computer and Software Skills
- Proficient in Microsoft office, Photoshop, Canva
- Social Media Marketing

## EXPERIENCE

### **CALL CENTER BILLING & SALES**

Dependable IT 2022

- Provide exceptional customer service and problem solving by responding to inbound calls
- Assist in billing calls- resolve bulling issues, clarify charges on their account, help them to make payments
- Identify where sales can be made, and push for sales on billing calls
- Resolve customer inquires
- · Work in fast paced, high volume, environment
- Multitask efficiently using several windows applications simultaneously

to verify customer information, determine the root cause of any issues and provide proper resolution

 Achieve performance goals for call time, accuracy, quality, deescalation, and customer satisfaction

### INDEPENDENT CONSULTANT

Arbonne

2022 - Present

- Explain products/services and prices and demonstrate use of products
   Write and record orders for merchandise or enter into computer
- Answer question about product features and benefits Distribute
- product samples or literature that benefits products or services

Teach and train other consultants skills and resources needed to be successful

#### **ADMINISTRATION**

Lav Bombs

2020-2022

- Ability to multitask while answering the phone, responding to emails and packing orders
- Create and sell Homemade luxury customizable bath bombs to customers using online website and social media platforms
- Advertise products via social media platforms
- Process and orgranize orders, shipping details or local orders to customers Create incentives, seasonal promotions, raffles and giveaways to increae customer loyalty and engagement

### **RETAIL STORE ASSOSICATE**

### Dollerama

2019-202

- · Greet customers and assist them in locating merchandise in store
- Process transactions using cash register and point of sale equipment
   Responsible for maintaining asile stock and cleanliness as well as
- roatating merchandise and inventory control

### Ardene

2015-2018

- Create a professional, continuing relationship with customers
- Immaculately resetting the floor throughout the day in order to curate a clean and professional atmosphere
- Managing transactions; sales, exchanges and returns
- Maintaining and organizing fitting rooms

Costa Blanca

2013-2014

- Greeting customers and resolve customer inquires Conduct all
- transactions including gift cards, refunds, and store credit Answer store phone calls and offer assistence accordingly • Maintain accurate and attractive merchandise displays, ensuring strategic placement of products in order to maximize purchases

# American Apparel 2021-2014

- Creating professional, continuing relationships with clients selecting
- clothing to fit various needs of every client Memorizing inventory and
- all information pertaining to product, including fabric used, washing
  instructions, stretch ability, availability, etc. Maintaining an organized
  fitting room; instructing the sales team on how to maximize sales,
  keeping track of all ingoing and outgoing clients as well as the sales
  associate assisting them, running clothes and utilizing staff as much as
  possible.
- Making transactions; sales, special orders, exchanges, repair orders, returns, etc.
- Immaculately resetting the floor throughout the day in order to curate the expected luxurious atmosphere.

# **VOULENTEER**

**Habitat For Humanity** 

#### 2012

- Re-Store:
- Greeting and assisting customers with locating merchandise in store
   Stocking merchandise while maintaining an organized store front Making transactions
- "Amazing Race Event"
- Responsible for setting up different event games and activities
- Managed various games; explaining rules to participants and ensuring a safe and fair environment
- Distributed food and beverages to participants
- Maintining cleanliness of station

### EDUCATION

### SECONDARY SCHOOL

Centennial College

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING TECHNOLOGY

2022 -current

Senece College

# BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION HUMAN RESOURCES

2016-2019

# HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

Oasis Alternative Secondary School

# REFERENCES

References Available Upon Request

# CERTIFICATIONS

- Smart Serve Certification
- Personal Training Specialist Certification CanFitPro